## Abdulrhman alhmrani, Secretary

Jeddah, Saudi Arabia, 054 144 5604, abdulrhmanalhmrani@gmail.com

LINKS	linkedin profile			
PROFILE	"Highly motivated law graduate from King Abdulaziz University with a 4.19 GPA. Over six years of diverse wor experience, starting at the age of 16, including significant roles in management and sales. Proven ability to handl various responsibilities and adapt to different work environments, showcasing strong leadership, organizationa and communication skills."			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Oct 2017 — Oct 2018	CUSTOMER CARE, Landmark			Jeddah
	At first, I worked as a cashier Then I handled. the customer complaints. because I was the only Saudi that worked at that branch Then I became the safe master. I worked more than 10 hours a day. when I was studying in high school. I learned a lot from that job.			
Feb 2019 — Aug 2019	SALES COORDINATOR, ALSOURY FLOORING AND FURNITURE			Jeddah
	This job was my first Peak in the business world In three months I got promoted To branch Manager I handle Government contracts. and private tour. and I built more than 17 mosque floors.			
Oct 2020 — Apr 2021	SELLER, VOX Cinema			Jeddah
	I worked in the kitchen And the ticket section. and the theater organizing.			
Dec 2021 — Jul 2022	SENIOR SALES ASSISTANT, Saudi French company			Jeddah
	<ul> <li>MANAGEMENT.</li> <li>I represented Brands like Dior and Boss and tom ford</li> <li>I learned how to work under pressure Because I worked. at the International Airport of Jeddah.</li> <li>I learned How to connect with people. from all over the world</li> </ul>			
Jul 2022 — Jun 2024	LEGAL SECRETARY, ROYA TRADING COMPANY  Jeddal			
	I handle the customer's legal papers			
	<ul> <li>And the owner's legal papers and the company papers.</li> <li>The monthly inventory check.</li> <li>The employer's complaints.</li> <li>The International Meeting Coordination.</li> <li>Answered phones and routed calls to the appropriate personnel</li> </ul>			
	•			
EDUCATION				
Jan 2020 — Jan 2024	Bachelor of Science in law, King Abdulaziz University  Jedda the most wonderful Education Experience The best thing I learned is I'm not gonna stop learning in my life.			
Feb 2024 — Feb 2024	63, piyas			Jeddah
	English test call step from qiy	7as		
SKILLS	Customer Service		Sales	
	Writing		Research	
	Microsoft Excel		Microsoft Word	
LANGUAGES	Arabic	Native speaker	English	Highly proficient
HOBBIES	Scuba diving snorkeling, rollerskate ice skate			